http://www.etsearch.com/footer/privacy

Tax Education
TaxConnections Privacy PolicyPlease read through TaxConnections Privacy Policy which has set high standards for privacy.
TAXCONNECTIONS PRIVACY POLICY - UPDATED FEBRUARY 2018
This privacy policy describes how TaxConnections Inc, a company incorporated in the State of Delaware, in the United States of America collects and uses the personal information you provide on our company website www.taxconnections.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.
COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
TaxConnections Never Sells Or Gives Away Your Personal Information
TaxConnections does NOT sell or give away your personal information, such as your name or e-mail address, that you provide or sign up for a TaxConnections Membership.
We will use your name and e-mail address only to send our content and our sponsors content to you through our client relationship management service.
You can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the foot of every page of the TaxConnections site.
As is typical of many other blogs and websites, this site may passively collect your personal information, such as your country of access, time of access, accessed posts and pages, etc., through the use of Google Analytics and/or the Jetpack WordPress Plugin.
This site does NOT sell or give away this information. TaxConnections Tax Blog is set up separately on WordPress from the rest of our site but our rules span our entire site.
We collect the following personal information from you:
Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, and phone number
Billing Information such as credit card number and billing address
Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, and password
We also collect the following information from you:
Information about your business such as company name, company size, and business type
Demographic information such as education, gender, interests and zip code
As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to:
Fulfill your order
Send you an order confirmation
Send you service information and updates
Respond to customer service requests
Administer your account
Send you a newsletter
Send you alerts and communications regarding our services
Respond to your questions and feedback
Improve our website to provide you with better services
Conduct research and analysis
Enable you to post your resume, search job postings, and contact or be contacted by prospective employers
List you in our publicly accessible, interactive “Worldwide Directory of Tax Professionals” if you are a subscribing member of this directory
SPONSORED LINKS
The TaxConnections site uses advertisements and sponsored links. TaxConnections does not control the content of the advertisements, sponsorships or the conduct of the third parties whose content is being served on our site. If you click on a sponsors ad and are taken to a third party website, please check that site’s privacy policy if you want to learn how your personal information is used by that site, including whether that site is tracking your behavior or clicks and whether that site is using cookies or other persistent identifiers.
If you click on a third party advertisement or one of our Sponsored links on this site and are taken to a third party’s website, that third party site may track information regarding your visit or collect personal information that you submit. TaxConnections does NOT have control over or knowledge of how or whether this occurs and you should read that site’s privacy policy if you want to learn about how your information may be used.
We take great pride in our ability to reach out to Sponsors to research their products and services prior to promoting them on the TaxConnections site. We encourage visitors to tell us of their experiences with these products and services. Your feedback is important to us and to our Sponsors in order to enable them to continually improve their products and services to customers.
CHOICE/OPT-OUT
You may choose to stop receiving our tax blog newsfeed, newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at support@taxconnections.com
We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.
TESTIMONIALS
We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personal information, such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent to post their name along with their testimonial prior to posting the testimonial. If you want to remove your personal information that is being displayed on the public-facing pages of our website, please send your request to support@taxconnections.com
TAX QUESTIONS, TAX POLLS AND FORUM
We provide you the opportunity to participate in tax questions, tax polls and forum on our site.
If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you. Participation in these areas is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.
The requested information typically includes contact information such as name and email address, and demographic information (such as zip code).
INFORMATION SHARING
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
We may also disclose your personal information:
As required by law to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
If TaxConnections Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information
To any other third party with your prior consent to do so
We make your contact information available to other users that you transact with on this site to help complete the transaction
For marketing purposes
THIRD PARTY E-COMMERCE SOLUTIONS PROVIDER
Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose.
COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.
If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.
THIRD PARTY COOKIES
The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and/or service providers is covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.
Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and/or service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.
WEB BEACONS
Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.
BEHAVIORAL TARGETING / RE-TARGETING
We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking Here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our Site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of TaxConnections. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.
DATA RETENTION
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at support@taxconnections.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
SECURITY
When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@taxconnections.com.
In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy policy and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy policy before providing your information.
ADDITIONAL POLICY INFORMATION
Social Media Widgets
Our website includes widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc.). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the widget. Cookies may also be set by the widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.
Blog and Forum
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@taxconnections.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
UPDATING/ACCESSING/AMENDING/CORRECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION
We do not store your submitted order information online for you to access. If you wish to correct, delete or change your submitted information there will be instructions provided within your order confirmation email or you may call or write to us support@taxconnections.com. Please see the "Contact Us" section at the end of this statement.
NOTIFICATION OF PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account - you are ultimately responsible for keeping your email address current at support@taxconnections.com), or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
CONTACT INFORMATION
You can contact us at:
Privacy Policy | Terms of Use | © Copyright 2010-2020 TaxConnections, Inc.® All Rights Reserved.
TaxConnections is where to find leading tax experts and tax resources worldwide.
PO Box 2389, La Jolla, California
858.999.0053
E-Mail Us
Contact Us Today
